(Amy:)No. You're supposed to be yourself,
not all desperate and creepy.
(Raj:)Okay, I'm getting
some mixed messages here.
(Amy:)Just say something normal like,
"I saw your profile.
"Looks like we have
a lot in common.
Let's get a cup of coffee sometime."
Yes. "Where I can be jealous of
the cup touching your ruby lips."
(Raj:)Or you just write it for me.
(Amy:)I'm not gonna pretend to be you.
(Raj:)I don't want you
to pretend to be me.
You can be my online wingman.
(Raj:)Like if we met her at a bar
and you talked me up.
(Amy:)Well, what would I say to her?
(Raj:)Just tell her what I'm really like.
(Raj:)And, if you think it'll help,
(Raj:)that you saw me changing once
and my package reminded you
(Raj:)of the muscular tail of a jaguar.
(Raj:)Use your own words.
(Sheldon:)Thanks again for taking me
to the pharmacy.